<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Robots on FTC 14607 - Robot Uprising</title>
    <link>/robots/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Robots on FTC 14607 - Robot Uprising</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/robots/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Our 2019-20 Robot: Firefly</title>
      <link>/robots/2019-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/robots/2019-20/</guid>
      <description>2020 Technical Binder  Robot Overview After a rolling development period of 6 months, mk. VII of Firefly was finalized. Utilizing the NASA BEST continuous design process, the team created a final robot that consists of a mecanum drivebase, double ball-bearing slide vertical extension, linkage-based horizontal extension, passthrough intake-outtake system, and a quick intake.
 Drivebase Firefly’s drivebase consists of a four wheel mecanum drivetrain in a full body acetal enclosure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our 2020-21 Robot: Axel the Donut Delivery Titan</title>
      <link>/robots/2020-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/robots/2020-21/</guid>
      <description>2020 Technical Binder  Robot Overview After a rolling development period of 6 months, Axel the Donut Delivery Titan was finalized. Utilizing the NASA BEST continuous design process, the team created an efficient final robot that consists of a mecanum drivebase, a drop down front roller intake, an gecko wheel intake transfer, a cage-like ring indexer, a two-side flywheel launcher, and a harness-like wobble goal grabber.
 Drivebase Axel’s drivebase consists of a four wheel mecanum drivetrain in a full body aluminum enclosure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our 2021-22 Robot: Osiris</title>
      <link>/robots/2021-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/robots/2021-22/</guid>
      <description>Updates will be posted soon! Be sure to check back!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
