<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Growing Up With Robots on FTC 14607 - Robot Uprising</title>
    <link>/gur/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Growing Up With Robots on FTC 14607 - Robot Uprising</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/gur/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Our 2019-20 Outreach</title>
      <link>/gur/2019-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gur/2019-20/</guid>
      <description>2020 Virtual Summer Camps The camps we held in the summer of 2020 were some of the most life-changing experiences for our team members, who were lucky enough to teach over 140 students each in two classes: CAD and Arduino/C++. Through these camps, we were able to raise $6000 in matched donations to FCPS purchase MiFi Hotspots and improve internet connectivty and accessibility for distance learning during the COVID-19 pandemic. We are sincerely grateful for all who have donated to help make such a feat possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our 2020-21 Outreach: Virtual Camps</title>
      <link>/gur/2020-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gur/2020-21/</guid>
      <description>TJHSST&amp;rsquo;s FIRST Tech Challenge Team 14607 Robot Uprising is proud to offer two free virtual spring camps, open to the community and general public. Classes are targeted at middle-school aged students, although anyone is free to attend and learn. These classes teach the fundamentals to technology and robotics, through CAD (Computer Aided Design), design principles, advanced manufacturing techniques, and programming in Python.
 Classes Each course runs for 6 Saturdays from 9:30-11:00 AM EDT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall 2021 Camps</title>
      <link>/gur/2021-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gur/2021-22/</guid>
      <description>Fall 2021 Camps TJHSST&amp;rsquo;s FIRST robotics team is hosting a series of free, virtual school-year classes for middle-school aged students on CAD (computer aided design) and robot programming in Python! These Saturday morning classes (9:30-11:00 am) will run from November 6th - December 4th. More info can be found in the flyer below; If you know of any students who may be interested (siblings, friends, etc), please don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to share this opportunity with them!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weyanoke Outreach!</title>
      <link>/gur/weyanoke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gur/weyanoke/</guid>
      <description>Weyanoke Outreach During Fall 2021 to Spring 2021, the TJHSST FTC Team went to Weyanoke weekly to teach Title 1 students about robotics.
We originally reached out to Weyanoke for a one time demonstration, but here we are today, helping them start not one, but two FIRST Lego League teams!
Exciting!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
