<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Team on FTC 14607 - Robot Uprising</title>
    <link>/team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Team on FTC 14607 - Robot Uprising</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 13:44:30 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Winston Gan</title>
      <link>/team/winstongan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/winstongan/</guid>
      <description>Winston is a senior in his 7th year of FIRST, joining FLL at the start because he wanted to experience programming. By joining an FLL team in 5th grade, his interest in robotics grew and it led him to join the FTC program, seeking to learn more about robotics. He is very excited to experience his third year on the team. In his free time, Winston enjoys playing basketball, making music, writing fictional novels, and is involved in TJ&amp;rsquo;s cyber patriot team and soccer team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evelyn Li</title>
      <link>/team/evelynli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/evelynli/</guid>
      <description>Evelyn is a junior in her second year of FIRST, joining after discovering CAD in a summer camp held by Team 14607. Evelyn enjoys programming and CAD-ing as well as the challenge and learning opportunities that FTC has to offer. Not only is she interested in robotics, but she is also an avid fan of National Geographic magazines (she collects them!) and physics (especially astrophysics!!). Evelyn enjoys art and is an editorial artist for tjTODAY&amp;ndash; TJ&amp;rsquo;s student newspaper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thrisha Sakamuri</title>
      <link>/team/thrishasakamuri/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/thrishasakamuri/</guid>
      <description>Thrisha is a senior in her fourth year at FIRST, being a part of her middle school’s FLL team, and joining because of her love of robots and business. She discovered her passion for STEM when she joined Science and Math Olympiad in fifth grade, and over the last five years, she has learned programming languages like Java, Python, and Arduino. In addition to robotics, Thrisha plays the piano, participates in Model United Nations, and plays lacrosse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan Jiang</title>
      <link>/team/alanjiang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/alanjiang/</guid>
      <description>Alan is a senior in his third year of FIRST and FTC team 14607, joining because of his love for all things robotics. He first started doing programming, then went down the path to robotics. He joined this team to learn more robotics from a great team. In addition to FTC, Alan does volunteering to teach elementary school kids robotics. During his free time, Alan enjoys playing video games, cooking, and reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Akul Dixit</title>
      <link>/team/akuldixit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/akuldixit/</guid>
      <description>Akul is a sophomore in his 2nd year of FTC. His first experiences with FIRST and robotics, in general, were in 1st grade when he saw his older brother build LEGO mindstorms robots in FLL, and he has been hooked to robotics ever since. He joined FTC team 14607 to join the unique community and gain new experiences in robotics. In addition to FTC, he likes to use CAD and 3D printers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Felix Howton</title>
      <link>/team/felixhowton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/felixhowton/</guid>
      <description>Felix is a junior in his third year of FIRST. In 8th grade, he discovered his love for robotics on his middle school FTC team while designing, constructing, and driving his team’s robot. Felix joined the team to dive deeper into robotics and to help the community learn about STEM. He is on the school&amp;rsquo;s history bowl team and his class’s class council. Felix loves spending his free time playing various sports including soccer, basketball, and ultimate frisbee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanvi Pedireddi</title>
      <link>/team/tanvipedireddi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/tanvipedireddi/</guid>
      <description>Tanvi is a junior and this is her fourth year in FIRST, joining because of a Facebook post and an aspiring interest in robotics and coding. She is on the school’s Lincoln Douglas debate team, and her hobbies include coding, singing, and drawing. She is looking forward to sophomore year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shirdi Palle</title>
      <link>/team/shirdipalle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/shirdipalle/</guid>
      <description>Shirdi is a freshman in her fourth year at FIRST, being a part of her FLL team from 3rd-6th grade. She joined because of her love of robots and innovation projects. She discovered her passion for STEM when she was attending STEM fairs as an elementary school student. In addition to robotics, Shirdi plays basketball, was a board member of a middle school business club, and was part of her middle school Technology Student Association.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rocco Zhang</title>
      <link>/team/roccozhang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/roccozhang/</guid>
      <description>Rocco is a sophomore in his second year of FTC, joining for his interest in coding. He found his passion for STEM when he joined Science Olympiad in sixth and eighth grade, and wanted to experience FIRST&amp;rsquo;s unique community by joining the team. Rocco also enjoys participating in debate, swimming, and playing video games in his free time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lindsay Hwang</title>
      <link>/team/lindsayhwang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/lindsayhwang/</guid>
      <description>Lindsay is a junior at TJHSST and this is her first year of FTC. She joined because of her interest in the programming aspect of robotics as well as seeing all the videos of the FIRST competitions. She enjoys programming and using CAD, and in her free time, she likes to run track, sing, and play lacrosse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anush Devkar</title>
      <link>/team/anushdevkar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/anushdevkar/</guid>
      <description>Anush is a freshman in his 1st year of FTC. His first experience with FIRST was in 4th grade when he participated in FLL. His passion for robotics was rediscovered in 6th grade, when he participated in VEX Robotics. He was fortunate enough to have the robotic parts stationed at his house, so Anush was able to work on building the robot outside of meeting times as well. Since then, his love for robotics and coding only grew.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AJ Seo</title>
      <link>/team/ajseo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 13:44:30 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/ajseo/</guid>
      <description>AJ is the captain of the team and senior in her 4th year of FIRST. She joined after competing in the class-wide IBET Robotics competition and discovering CAD and computer science! She&amp;rsquo;s been passionate in STEM since her science bowl and olympiad years in middle school and has been striving to continue that path at TJ. In the past couple years, AJ has loved being able to connect with the community through outreach and teaching younger students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Wu</title>
      <link>/team/charliewu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/charliewu/</guid>
      <description>Charlie is a senior in his 9th year of FIRST, joining the program due to his early inclination towards robotics; starting FLL in fourth grade. He is the founder &amp;amp; team captain of Team 14607, with five years of experience in FTC. He started the team with his dream of crafting a diverse, robot-loving family, and looking at our team, can confidently say that we have done it! In addition to FTC, Charlie dances urban hip-hop and is an officer of Jefferson’s Urban Dance Movement, is captain of Jefferson’s Machine Learning Club, and pursues advanced robotics autonomy research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dev Patel</title>
      <link>/team/devpatel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/devpatel/</guid>
      <description>Dev is a senior in his 8th year of FIRST, joining the FLL program in 5th grade due to his love of legos. Dev is the CAD Lead of team FTC 14607, and has 5 years of FTC experience. He joined the team looking for a diverse, robotics family. In addition to FTC, Dev is part of the TJ UROV Team, and pursues his interests in Cloud Computing and the AWS Platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jacob Consalvi</title>
      <link>/team/jacobconsalvi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/jacobconsalvi/</guid>
      <description>Jacob is a senior and this is his fourth year in FIRST, joining after discovering this gem-of-a-program in fourth grade for FLL and it has shaped him as a person and built his character. A founding member of Robot Uprising, he is a member of the CAD, Engineering, and Software subteams. He has amazing EUREKA moments and amazing extensive knowledge of manufacturing. He participates in FRC, CubeSat, Computer Vision, TARC. Jacob has really cool calligraphy pens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jason Wang</title>
      <link>/team/jasonwang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/jasonwang/</guid>
      <description>Jason is a senior in his 3rd year of FIRST, and he developed a passion for robotics after discovering the technological wonder that is CAD. He is the Documentation and Outreach Lead, and his favorite parts about our robotics team are designing new parts, engaging with other robot-lovers, and teaching younger students. Besides robotics, Jason participates in TJ’s Machine Learning Club, Senior Computer Team, Dev Club, and Urban Dance Movement. He has an avid interest in computer science and dreams of using CS and robotics to help others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kari Naga</title>
      <link>/team/karinaga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/karinaga/</guid>
      <description>Kari is a senior in his 3rd year of FIRST. A founding member of Robot Uprising, he has been interested in robotics since elementary school but wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to explore it until he joined FTC. He is passionate about programming and building and also enjoys the outreach portions of the FIRST program. Outside of FTC, he is an officer of the web development club at TJ and enjoys playing video games and listening to music in his free time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krish Patel</title>
      <link>/team/krishpatel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/krishpatel/</guid>
      <description>Krish is a senior and this is his eighth year in FIRST, joining FLL in 5th grade because he loves robotics and FIRST is a global venue to meet others about it! He is a member of the Build and Design subteams, and assembles the team’s design. FUN FACT: Dev and Krish are identical twins!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neil Mehra</title>
      <link>/team/neilmehra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/neilmehra/</guid>
      <description>Neil is a junior in his 4th year of FIRST. He first experienced robotics as a kid through LEGO Mindstorms and has had a passion for it ever since then. In 8th grade he founded an FTC team to pursue robotics, which eventually led to meeting Robot Uprising and joining them next year. Besides FTC, Neil likes to compete in programming competitions. During his free time Neil makes custom keyboards and plays video games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Punav Kheterpal</title>
      <link>/team/punavkheterpal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/punavkheterpal/</guid>
      <description>Punav is a freshman and is participating in his fourth year of FIRST, joining the FLL program due to his love of programming and robotics. He joined the team looking for a new opportunity to pursue his interest in robotics and programming. In addition to the FTC team Punav is participating in the neuroscience society and the quiz bowl team. He is interested in how the human body works on an anatomical and molecular level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reevu Adakroy</title>
      <link>/team/reevuadakroy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/reevuadakroy/</guid>
      <description>Reevu is a senior in his 3rd year of FIRST, joining the FTC program in 10th grade due to his interest in building things. Ever since he worked with his 8th grade Science Olympiad team to make a hovercraft, Reevu has loved creating things that move. Reevu is the Design Lead of team FTC 14607, with 3 years of experience. He joined the team looking for a community that shares his passion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Johnathan Tong</title>
      <link>/team/johnathantong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/johnathantong/</guid>
      <description>Johnathan is a junior in his 4th year of FTC. In 7th grade, he built a 3D printer and was immediately hooked onto robotics and engineering. Johnathan joined the team because he wanted to explore robotics and teach his community with a passionate team. During his free time, Johnathan enjoys playing chess, reading books, playing and watching video games, and learning new things. He also enjoys staying hydrated and eating pizza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maribelle</title>
      <link>/team/maribellechu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/maribellechu/</guid>
      <description>Maribelle is a sophomore in her first year of FTC. Her love for engineering, Arduino, tech, and outreach is why she joined FTC. Working with a team of passionate members to promote and partake in STEM is her favorite part about FTC. Outside of FTC, Maribelle codes websites, plays soccer on her club and varsity school team, manages a library center for GIVE, listens to music, competes in Japan Bowl, composes songs, reads many books, and learns as much as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/team/aidencheong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/aidencheong/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
