<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Team on Robot Uprising</title>
    <link>www.robotuprising.org/team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Team on Robot Uprising</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="www.robotuprising.org/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dev Patel</title>
      <link>www.robotuprising.org/team/devpatel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.robotuprising.org/team/devpatel/</guid>
      <description>Dev is a senior and this is his eight year in FIRST, joining after finding this program that would facilitate his journey of engineering in 5th grade for FLL. He is the CAD Lead and as a member of the Design subteam, he oversees our team Fusion CAD of the robot. Dev’s most accomplished moments include when he fully automated his homelab, and became an AWS Certified Solutions Architect. In addition to FTC, Dev is also a member of Jefferson&amp;rsquo;s UROV Team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Wu</title>
      <link>www.robotuprising.org/team/charliewu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.robotuprising.org/team/charliewu/</guid>
      <description>Charlie is a senior and this is his ninth year in FIRST, joining the program due to his early inclination towards all subjects robotics related, starting FLL in fourth grade. He is one of the team captains and a veteran of FTC with five years of experience. He started the team with his dream of crafting a diverse robot-loving family and, when looking at our current team demographic, can confidently say that we have done it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jacob Consalvi</title>
      <link>www.robotuprising.org/team/jacobconsalvi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.robotuprising.org/team/jacobconsalvi/</guid>
      <description>Jacob is a junior and this is his second year in FIRST, joining after discovering this gem-of-a-program in fourth grade for FLL and it has shaped him as a person and built his character. He is the Build Lead and as a member of the CAD and Software subteam, he has amazing EUREKA moments and amazing extensive knowledge of manufacturing. He participates in FRC, CubeSat, Computer Vision, TARC. Jacob has really cool calligraphy pens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kari Naga</title>
      <link>www.robotuprising.org/team/karinaga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.robotuprising.org/team/karinaga/</guid>
      <description>Kari is a senior and this is his third year in FIRST, joining after seeing the team’s convincing Facebook post advertising for new members and continued with the team because of all the fun memories we have made! As a member of the Software and Design subteams, he CADs, and designs the mechanisms as well as codes the robot. In school Kari participates in the Web Development Club and loves coding!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reevu Adakroy</title>
      <link>www.robotuprising.org/team/reevuadakroy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.robotuprising.org/team/reevuadakroy/</guid>
      <description>Reevu is a senior and this is his third year in FIRST, joining because he thought the program was super cool and an experience that would allow him to apply the knowledge he learned in school! He is the Design Head and a member of the Build subteam, where he designs and brainstorms robot subsystems. In his free time, he practices solving Rubik&amp;rsquo;s Cubes and his best time is 15 seconds and works out at the nearby recenter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krish Patel</title>
      <link>www.robotuprising.org/team/krishpatel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.robotuprising.org/team/krishpatel/</guid>
      <description>Krish is a senior and this is his eigth year in FIRST, joining FLL in 5th grade because he loves robotics and FIRST is a global venue to meet others about it! He is the Drivetrain Head and as a member of the Build subteam, he is in charge of our drop center drive train, as well as assemble the team’s design. FUN FACT: Dev and Krish are identical twins!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AJ Seo</title>
      <link>www.robotuprising.org/team/ajseo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.robotuprising.org/team/ajseo/</guid>
      <description>AJ is a junior and this is her third year in FIRST. She decided to join TJ’s FTC team after enjoying her time with the FRC team in her freshman year. Outside of school, AJ is on the school’s tennis team and club. She is a part of class council and enjoys planning events with the other members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jason Wang</title>
      <link>www.robotuprising.org/team/jasonwang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.robotuprising.org/team/jasonwang/</guid>
      <description>Jason is a senior and this is his third year in FIRST, joining after being roped in by our ever-successfully persuasive Facebook post (see above) and has stuck around because he loves the interactive builder-robot experience. As a member of the Engineering and Build subteam as well as the Software Team, he assists the programming and he orchestrates (get it, because he does orchestra) the development of the mechanisms. He participates in ICT (Computer Team) and plays bridge!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neil Mehra</title>
      <link>www.robotuprising.org/team/neilmehra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.robotuprising.org/team/neilmehra/</guid>
      <description>Neil is a sophomore and this is his third year in FIRST, joining after finding the team through competing against them in states. In his free time Neil likes to build keyboards and grind Overwatch. As a member of the team Neil programs scuffed autos that mimic GF. In school Neil wants to do ROV, Botball, and play league in a room of sweats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winston Gan</title>
      <link>www.robotuprising.org/team/winstongan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.robotuprising.org/team/winstongan/</guid>
      <description>Winston is a sophomore and this is his third year in FIRST, joining after being roped in by our ever-successfully persuasive Facebook post (see Jason) and has stuck around because he loves the interactive builder-robot experience. He likes to make music in his free time and he plays soccer and basketball. He thinks that his music is better than it actually is</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>