<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sponsorship on Robot Uprising</title>
    <link>/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sponsorship on Robot Uprising</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 15:14:39 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Perspecta Case Study</title>
      <link>/services/perspecta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/perspecta/</guid>
      <description>Perspecta is the result of a merger between 3 defense contractors - Vencore, DXE, and Keypoint. This company has been around since 2017, and is now the 7th largest defense contractor in the nation, signing deals worth billions of dollars.
We are extremely grateful for their support, and we have worked together in many aspects of the team, as outlined below. Our mentors from Perspecta include Mr. Barry Barlow (CIO), Mrs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TJPF Case Study</title>
      <link>/services/tjpf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/tjpf/</guid>
      <description>The TJ Partnership Fund (TJPF) is our schools grant system to support the unique learning opportunities, specialized curriculum, and innovative research opportunities that TJHSST provides. While they normally have a maximum grant of $1,000 for clubs, due to our performance at the world championship, and our extensive outreach, we were given $5,000 dollars. To show our gratitude, we partnered with them for multiple events, including Techstravaganza and the TJHSST Partnership Gala</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsorship Packet</title>
      <link>/services/sponsorshippacket/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/sponsorshippacket/</guid>
      <description>If you are Interested in sponsoring our Team, please refer to our sponsorhip packet: https://tinyurl.com/ftc14607sponsor</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>